by RentAnAdviser.com
Last Christmas‚ I gave you my heart
But the very next day you gave it away
This year‚ to save me from tears
I will give it to someone special
Last Christmas‚ I gave you my heart
But the very next day you gave it away
This year‚ to save me from tears
I will give it to someone special
Once bitten and twice shy
I keep my distance
But you still catch my eye
Tell me baby
Do you recognize me?
Well‚ It is been a year
It doesn′t surprise me
I wrapped it up and sent it
With a note saying I love
you I meant it
Now I know what a fool I have been
But if you kissed me now
I know You had fool me again
Last Christmas‚ I gave you my heart
But the very next day you gave it away
This year‚ to save me from tears
I will give it to someone special
Last Christmas‚ I gave you my heart
But the very next day you gave it away
This year‚ to save me from tears
I will give it to someone special
A crowded room‚ friends
with tired eyes
I am hiding from you‚ and
your soul of ice
My god I thought you were
someone to rely on
Me? I guess I was a shoulder to cry on
A face on a lover with
a fire in his heart
A man under cover but
you tore me apart
Now I have found a real love
you′ll never fool me again
Last Christmas‚ I gave you my heart
But the very next day you gave it away
This year‚ to save me from tears
I will give it to someone special
Last Christmas‚ I gave you my heart
But the very next day you gave it away
This year‚ to save me from tears
I will give it to someone special
A face on a lover with
a fire in his heart
A man under cover but
you tore him apart
Maybe next year I will
give it to someone
I will give it to someone special
www.RentAnAdviser.com