by RentAnAdviser.com
I don′t want a lot for Christmas
There is just one thing I need
I don′t care about the presents
Underneath the Christmas tree
I just want you for my own
More than you could ever know
Make my wish come true oh
All I want for Christmas is you
I don′t want a lot for Christmas
There is just one thing I need‚ and I
Don′t care about the presents
Underneath the Christmas tree
I don′t need to hang my stocking
There upon the fireplace
Santa Claus won′t make me happy
With a toy on Christmas day
I just want you for my own
More than you could ever know
Make my wish come true
All I want for Christmas is you
I won′t ask for much this Christmas
I won′t even wish for snow‚ and I
I just wanna keep on waiting
Underneath the mistletoe
I won′t make a list and send it
To the North Pole for Saint Nick
I won′t even stay awake
To hear those magic reindeer click
′Cause I just want you here tonight
Holding on to me so tight
What more can I do
Oh‚ Baby all I want for
Christmas is you
All the lights are shining
So brightly everywhere
And the sound of children′s
Laughter fills the air
And everyone is singing
I hear those sleigh bells ringing
Santa won′t you bring me
The one I really need
Won′t you please bring my
baby to me quickly
I don′t want a lot for Christmas
This is all I am asking for
I just wanna see my baby
Standing right outside my door
I just want you for my own
More than you could ever know
Make my wish come true
Baby all I want for Christmas is you
All I want for Christmas is you‚ baby
www.RentAnAdviser.com